Guide to the American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council 1707 Records WAG.298
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: General Administrative and Locals Files, 1950-2006
  - Local 389: Living Wage Bill--Westchester, 2002, undated; cuid6580 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Local 389: Long Island Office, 2000-2001; cuid6581 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Local 389: Membership Meetings, 2002-2003; cuid6582 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Local 389: Negotiations--Jewish Association for Services for the Aged (JASA), Association for Services for the Aged, Services for the Aged, 1984-1988; cuid6583 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Local 389: Office and Professional Employees International Union (OPEIU), Local 153, 2004; cuid6584 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Local 389: Organizing, 1986, undated; cuid6585 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Local 389: Personal Care Level I (Housekeeper Program)--NYC Medicaid, 1990-1991; cuid6586 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Local 389: Wages and Benefits, [1998]; cuid6587 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Local 1881: Memoranda, 1997; cuid6588 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Retirees Chapter: AFSCME, 1983-1998, undated; cuid6589 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Retirees Chapter: Benefits, 1990, undated; cuid6590 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Retirees Chapter: Clippings, 1979-1996, undated; cuid6591 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Retirees Chapter: Congress of Senior Citizens of Greater New York, 1996, undated; cuid6592 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Retirees Chapter: Constitution, 1980-1989, undated; cuid6593 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Retirees Chapter: Correspondence, 1980-1999; cuid6594 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Retirees Chapter: Correspondence--Memoranda, 1995-1998; cuid6595 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Retirees Chapter: DC 1707, 1982-1997, undated; cuid6596 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Retirees Chapter: Ephemera, Notes, 1987-1996, undated; cuid6597 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Retirees Chapter: Events (Non-AFSCME, DC 1707), [1980-1996]; cuid6598 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Retirees Chapter: Excursions, 1995-1997, undated; cuid6599 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Retirees Chapter: Flyers, Handouts, 1981-1998, undated; cuid6600 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Retirees Chapter: Health Care, 1986-1997, undated; cuid6601 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Retirees Chapter: Human Services Providers Advisory Committee, 1990, undated; cuid6602 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Retirees Chapter: Meetings, 1980-1983; cuid6603 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Retirees Chapter: Meetings, 1984; cuid6604 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Retirees Chapter: Meetings, 1985; cuid6605 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Retirees Chapter: Meetings, Jan-May 1986; cuid6606 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Retirees Chapter: Meetings, Jun-Dec 1986; cuid6607 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Retirees Chapter: Meetings, 1987; cuid6608 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Retirees Chapter: Meetings, 1988; cuid6609 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Retirees Chapter: Meetings, 1989; cuid6610 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Retirees Chapter: Meetings, 1990; cuid6611 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Retirees Chapter: Meetings, 1991; cuid6612 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Retirees Chapter: Meetings, 1992; cuid6613 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Retirees Chapter: Meetings, 1993; cuid6614 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Retirees Chapter: Meetings, 1994; cuid6615 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Retirees Chapter: Meetings, 1995-1997; cuid6616 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Retirees Chapter: Meetings--Notices, Memoranda, 1981-2000; cuid6617 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Retirees Chapter: Members, 1985-1998; cuid6618 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Retirees Chapter: National Council of Senior Citizens/New York State Council of Senior Citizens, 1981-1996, undated; cuid6619 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Retirees Chapter: New York City/State, Undated; cuid6620 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Retirees Chapter: Notices to New Retirees, 1981-1996, undated; cuid6621 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Retirees Chapter: Retirement Planning, 1982, undated; cuid6622 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Retirees Chapter: Southern Poverty Law Center, 1993-1995; cuid6623 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Floppy disk (Women's Affairs Committee), Undated; cuid6624 (Box 47)
- Series III: Agency Files, 1947-2007
  Agency files document Local 1707/DC 1707's relationships with its members' workplaces. Bargaining material includes contracts, agreements and other signed documents, negotiation material, correspondence and memoranda, and notes relating to the collective bargaining process. Grievance files document individual and group grievances against employers. Personnel files generally contain information about workplace staff, hiring, firing, and positions. General Administrative material includes meeting notices, correspondence, and other administrative items. DC 1707 Staff Representative files contain copies of outgoing staff representative correspondence and memoranda involving administrative issues, including bargaining, grievances, and meetings. Affiliated locals are listed in parenthesis when known.
  - Abbott House, Inc.: Bargaining (Local 215), [1984]; cuid6625 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Altro Health and Rehabilitation Services: Bargaining (Local 215), 1975-1977; cuid6626 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - American Committee on Africa: Bargaining (Local 107), 1993; cuid6627 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - American Committee on Africa: Grievance--Sandy Boyer (Local 107), 1995; cuid6628 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - American Friends of the Hebrew University, Inc.: Bargaining (Local 107), 1996; cuid6629 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - American Jewish Committee: Grievances, Correspondence (Local 107), 1995-1996; cuid6630 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - American Jewish Congress: Bargaining (Local 107), 1995-1996; cuid6631 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Amit Women, Inc.: Bargaining (Local 107), 1996; cuid6632 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Angel Guardian Home: Bargaining (Local 215), 1995-1996; cuid6633 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Angel Guardian Home: Grievance (Local 215), 1995-1999; cuid6634 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Associated YM and YWHAs of Greater New York: Bargaining (Local 215), 1959-1975; cuid6635 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Associated YM and YWHAs of Greater New York: Grievance (Local 215), 1964; cuid6636 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Association for Services for the Aged: Bargaining (Local 389), 2001; cuid6637 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Association for the Help of Retarded Children: Bargaining (Local 253), [1986], 1995-2000; cuid6638 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Association for the Help of Retarded Children: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 253), 1995-2000; cuid6639 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Bank Street College of Education: Bargaining (Local 253), 1961-1968; cuid6640 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Bank Street College of Education: Bargaining (Local 253), 1969-1976; cuid6641 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Bank Street College of Education: Bargaining (Local 253), 1980-1986; cuid6642 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Bank Street College of Education: Bargaining (Local 253), 1988-1998; cuid6643 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Bank Street College of Education: Bargaining (Local 253), 2000-2007; cuid6644 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Bank Street College of Education: Grievances (Local 253), 1995-2000; cuid6645 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Belle and Samuel Rose YM-YWHA of Southern Westchester: Bargaining (Local 253), 1996; cuid6646 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Belle and Samuel Rose YM-YWHA of Southern Westchester: Grievances (Local 253), 1994-1999; cuid6647 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Belle and Samuel Rose YM-YWHA of Southern Westchester: Personnel, General Administrative (Local 253), 1994-1998; cuid6648 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - B'Nai B'Rith International/B'Nai B'Rith Youth Organization: Bargaining (Local 107), 1989-1996; cuid6649 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Board of Jewish Education: Bargaining (Local 253), 1948-1975; cuid6650 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Board of Jewish Education: Bargaining (Local 253), 1975-1989; cuid6651 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Board of Jewish Education: Bargaining (Local 253), 1990-2005; cuid6652 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Board of Jewish Education: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 253), 1995; cuid6653 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Boro Park YM and YWHA Senior Center: Bargaining (Local 215), 1996; cuid6654 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Boro Park YM and YWHA Senior Center: Grievance--Chaim Nachman (Local 215), 1999; cuid6655 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Boro Park YM and YWHA Senior Center: Personnel (Local 215), cuid6656 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Bowery Residents Committee (BRC) Human Services Corporation: Bargaining (Local 215), 1991-1997; cuid6657 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Bowery Residents Committee (BRC) Human Services Corporation: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 215), 1996; cuid6658 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Bowery Residents Committee (BRC) Human Services Corporation: Grievances (Local 215), 1999; cuid6659 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Bronx House Jewish Community Center: Bargaining (Local 215), 1996; cuid6660 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Bronx House Jewish Community Center: Grievances/Personnel Issues (Local 215), 1994-1998; cuid6661 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Bronx House Jewish Community Center: Grievances--Teachers Vacation (Local 215), 1994-1996; cuid6662 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Bronx House Jewish Community Center: Grievance--Davis, Hernowitz, and Nadel (Local 215), 1996-1999; cuid6663 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Bushwick Economic Development Vendor Agency: Bargaining (Local 389), 2001; cuid6664 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - [Center for Employment Opportunities?] (CEO): General Administrative, 1998; cuid6665 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Central Queens YM-YWHA: Bargaining (Local 215), 1975, 1996; cuid6666 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Central Queens YM-YWHA: Grievances (Local 215), 1994-1998; cuid6667 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Central Queens YM-YWHA: Grievance--Myron Fulton (Local 215), 1993-1998; cuid6668 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Central Queens YM-YWHA: Personnel (Local 215), 1994-1999, undated; cuid6669 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Children's Aid Society: Election Materials, Feb 1998; cuid6670 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Children's Corner Day Care Center, Inc.: Bargaining [Local 205], [1996]; cuid6671 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Concourse House: Personnel Policy Manual, [1998]; cuid6672 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Consortium for Worker Education (CWE): Wage Subsidy Program, 2002, undated; cuid6673 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Council of Jewish Federations (CJF): Bargaining (Local 107), 1995-1999; cuid6674 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Council of Jewish Federations (CJF): Merger with United Jewish Appeal (Local 107), 1998-1999; cuid6675 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Council of Jewish Federations (CJF): Personnel (Local 107), 1997-1999; cuid6676 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Development Corporation for Israel: Bargaining (Local 107, Local 1881), 1953-1962; cuid6677 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Development Corporation for Israel: Bargaining (Local 107, Local 1881), 1963-1967; cuid6678 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Development Corporation for Israel: Bargaining (Local 107, Local 1881), 1969-1975; cuid6679 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Development Corporation for Israel: Bargaining (Local 107, Local 1881), 1976-[1981]; cuid6680 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Development Corporation for Israel: Bargaining (Local 107, Local 1881), [1983]-1987; cuid6681 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Development Corporation for Israel: Bargaining (Local 107, Local 1881), [1989]-[1994]; cuid6682 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Development Corporation for Israel: Bargaining (Local 107, Local 1881), 1994-1999; cuid6683 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Development Corporation for Israel: General Administrative/Personnel (Local 107, Local 1881), 1999-2000; cuid6684 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Development Corporation for Israel: Grievances (Local 107, Local 1881), 1995-2000; cuid6685 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Development Corporation for Israel: Grievances (Local 107, Local 1881), 1996-1997; cuid6686 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - District Council 1707 Professional Employees Union: Bargaining, 1977-1993; cuid6687 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - District Council 1707 Professional Employees Union: Bargaining, 1977-1997; cuid6688 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - East New York YM and YWHA: Bargaining, 1956-[1963]; cuid6689 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - East Tremont YM and YWHA: Bargaining, 1954-1956; cuid6690 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Educational Alliance: Bargaining (Local 215), [1991]-1997; cuid6691 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Educational Alliance: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 215), 1995-1997; cuid6692 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Educational Alliance: Grievance (Local 215), 1955; cuid6693 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - HR Dynamics, Inc. (FEGS and NYANA): General Administrative, Grievances (Local 215), 2000, 2004; cuid6694 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Family Service Society of Yonkers: Bargaining (Local 389), 1998-[2001]; cuid6695 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEG) [Federation Employment Service]: Bargaining (Local 215), [1950]-1953; cuid6696 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Bargaining (Local 215), 1955-1962; cuid6697 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Bargaining (Local 215), 1964-1975; cuid6698 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Bargaining (Local 215), 1977-1981; cuid6699 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Bargaining (Local 215), 1981-1983; cuid6700 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Bargaining (Local 215), 1985-1988; cuid6701 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Bargaining (Local 215), 1988-1989; cuid6702 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Bargaining (Local 215), 1990-1999; cuid6703 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Bargaining (Local 215), 2000; cuid6704 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): DC 1707 Staff Representative Files; General Administrative (Local 215), 1995-1996; cuid6705 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Flyers (Local 215), [1996-1999]; cuid6706 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Grievances (Local 215), 1994-1996; cuid6707 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Grievances (Local 215), 1994-1997; cuid6708 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Grievances (Local 215), 1995-1996; cuid6709 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Grievances (Local 215), 1997; cuid6710 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Grievances (Local 215), 1998-1999; cuid6711 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Grievances (Local 215), 2000-2001; cuid6712 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Grievances--Mike Davis, Donald Monaco (Local 215), 1985-1995; cuid6713 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Grievance--George Goldson (Local 215), 1990-1995; cuid6714 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Grievance--Jannie Terry (Local 215), 1996-1997; cuid6715 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Personnel/General Administrative (Local 215), 1995-1997; cuid6716 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Personnel--Layoff Notices (Local 215), 1995; cuid6717 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Personnel--Layoff Notices (Local 215), 1995; cuid6718 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Personnel--Layoff Notices (Local 215), 1996; cuid6719 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Personnel--Layoff Notices (Local 215), 1997; cuid6720 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Federation Group Work Agencies: Bargaining (Local 215), 1956-1963; cuid6721 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Federation Group Work Agencies: Bargaining (Local 215), 1965-2000; cuid6722 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Federation Group Work Agencies: Bargaining (Local 215), 1968-1975; cuid6723 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Federation Group Work Agencies: Bargaining (Local 215), 1971-1988; cuid6724 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Federation Group Work Agencies: Bargaining (Local 215), 1977-1988; cuid6725 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Federation Group Work Agencies: Bargaining (Local 215), 1993-1999; cuid6726 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Federation Group Work Agencies: Bargaining (Local 215), 1994-1997; cuid6727 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Federation Group Work Agencies: Bargaining (Local 215), 1996-1998; cuid6728 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Federation Group Work Agencies: Bargaining (Local 215), 1999-2000; cuid6729 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Federation Group Work Agencies: Bargaining (Local 215), 2006; cuid6730 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Federation Group Work Agencies: General Administrative, Grievances (Local 215), 1992-2000; cuid6731 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Federation Group Work Agencies: Grievances (Local 215), 1992-1999; cuid6732 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies (FOJP) Service Corporation: Bargaining (Local 107), 1979-1981; cuid6733 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies (FOJP) Service Corporation: Bargaining (Local 107), 1984-1988; cuid6734 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies (FOJP) Service Corporation: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files, General Administrative (Local 107), 1994-1998; cuid6735 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies (FOJP) Service Corporation: Grievances (I) (Local 107), 1994-2000; cuid6736 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies (FOJP) Service Corporation: Grievances (II) (Local 107), 1994-2000; cuid6737 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies (FOJP) Service Corporation: Grievances--Sonia Flanagan (Local 107), 1997-1998; cuid6738 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies (FOJP) Service Corporation: Grievances--Arnold Grab (Local 107), 1994-1997; cuid6739 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies (FOJP) Service Corporation: Grievances--Nanette Norwood (Local 107), 1993-1994; cuid6740 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies (FOJP) Service Corporation: Grievances--Gaetana J. Vega (Local 107), 1989-1997; cuid6741 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies (FOJP) Service Corporation: Personnel--Monthly Reports (Local 107), 1993-1994; cuid6742 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies (FOJP) Service Corporation: Personnel--Monthly Reports (Local 107), 1995; cuid6743 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies (FOJP) Service Corporation: Personnel--Monthly Reports (Local 107), 1996; cuid6744 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies (FOJP) Service Corporation: Personnel--Monthly Reports (Local 107), 1997; cuid6745 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies (FOJP) Service Corporation: Personnel--Monthly Reports (Local 107) (I), 1998; cuid6746 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies (FOJP) Service Corporation: Personnel--Monthly Reports (Local 107) (II), 1998; cuid6747 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies (FOJP) Service Corporation: Personnel--Monthly Reports (Local 107), 1999-2000; cuid6748 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Federation of the Handicapped: Organizing Campaign(Local 389), 1990, undated; cuid6749 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Ferncliff Manor for the Retarded: Bargaining--Unfair Labor Practices, 1995-1999; cuid6750 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Ferncliff Manor for the Retarded: Bargaining--Unfair Labor Practices, 1997-1999; cuid6751 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Ferncliff Manor for the Retarded: Bargaining--Unfair Labor Practices (NLRB Case), 1997-1999; cuid6752 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Fountain House: Grievances, 1999; cuid6753 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - GHI Home Care Services: Bargaining (Local 389), 1983-1989; cuid6754 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - GHI Home Health Homemaker Services: Bargaining (Local 389), 1979; cuid6755 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Grand Street Settlement: Bargaining (DC 1707 Staff Representative Files)(Local 107), 1995-1996; cuid6756 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Gustave Hartman YM and YWHA: General Administrative, 1995; cuid6757 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Hadassah: Bargaining (Local 107), 1950-1959; cuid6758 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Hadassah: Bargaining (Local 107), 1960-1968; cuid6759 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Hadassah: Bargaining/DC 1707 Staff Representative File (Local 107), 1992-1995; cuid6760 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Hale House Center: Bargaining (Local 215), 2005; cuid6761 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Hebrew Educational Society: Bargaining (Local 215), 1971, 1975; cuid6762 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Hebrew Educational Society: Bargaining (Local 215), 1995-1996; cuid6763 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Hebrew Educational Society: Grievances (Local 215), 1995-1997; cuid6764 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Hebrew Educational Society: Personnel (Local 215), 1994-2000; cuid6765 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Hebrew Immigrant Aid Society (HIAS): Bargaining (Local 215), 1952-1959; cuid6766 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Hebrew Immigrant Aid Society (HIAS): Bargaining (Local 215), 1961-1978; cuid6767 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Hebrew Immigrant Aid Society (HIAS): Bargaining (Local 215), 1980-1982; cuid6768 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Hebrew Immigrant Aid Society (HIAS): Bargaining (Local 215), 1986-1990; cuid6769 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Hebrew Immigrant Aid Society (HIAS): Bargaining (Local 215), 1992; cuid6770 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Hebrew Immigrant Aid Society (HIAS): Bargaining (Local 215), 1994-1995; cuid6771 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Hebrew Immigrant Aid Society (HIAS): Bargaining (Local 215), 1994-1995; cuid6772 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Hebrew Immigrant Aid Society (HIAS): Bargaining (Local 215), 1998-2002; cuid6773 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Hebrew Immigrant Aid Society (HIAS): Bargaining (Local 215), 2007; cuid6774 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Hebrew Immigrant Aid Society (HIAS): Ephemera (Local 215), Undated; cuid6775 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Hebrew Immigrant Aid Society (HIAS): General Administrative (Local 215), [1968]; cuid6776 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Hebrew Immigrant Aid Society (HIAS): Personnel/Grievances (Local 215), 1994-1999; cuid6777 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Hebrew Immigrant Aid Society (HIAS): Personnel/Grievances (Local 215), 1995-1997; cuid6778 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Henry Street Settlement, 1979; cuid6779 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Highbridge Advisory Council: General Administrative, 1997-1998; cuid6780 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Home Assistance Personnel Inc.: Bargaining (Local 389), 1997-2000; cuid6781 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Home Attendant Vendor Agency, Inc. (HAVA): Bargaining (Local 389), 1984-[2001]; cuid6782 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Homes for the Homeless: Complaint Against DC 1707, 1994; cuid6783 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Hope House, Inc.: Organizing, 1999; cuid6784 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Hudson Guild: Bargaining (Local 215), 2006; cuid6785 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Huntington Freedom Center: Bargaining, Grievance (DC 1707 Staff Representative Files) (Local 253), 1995-1997; cuid6786 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Institute for Urban Family Health: Bargaining, 1998; cuid6787 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Institute of International Education: Bargaining. Grievances (DC 1707 Staff Representative Files) (Local 253), 1995-1997; cuid6788 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions: Bargaining, 1960-1968; cuid6789 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - International Rescue Committee: Bargaining (Local 215), 1950-1971; cuid6790 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - International Rescue Committee: Bargaining (Local 215), 1972-1988; cuid6791 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - International Rescue Committee: Bargaining (Local 215), 1990-2002; cuid6792 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - International Rescue Committee: Personnel, Grievances (Local 215), 1994-1997; cuid6793 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Jewish Association for Services for the Aged (JASA): Bargaining (Local 215), 1971-1983; cuid6794 (Box 23, Folder 24)